Jacob Brekken

Information Technology

Hardworking, and devoted University of North Texas student, working towards his goal of obtaining a bachelor's degree in **Information Technology**. 3+ years of experience and interested in internships and jobs in the meantime to help gain insight and expand my knowledge of my field.

Experience

06/2022present

Network Operations Center Technician

Provision Data Services, Dallas, TX

- Install and maintain network infrastructure and collect network performance data
- Collaborate with field technicians and IT teams to resolve network issues

05/2019-09/2019

Technical Lead

iCode, Southlake, TX

- Worked as the main instructor for teaching kids' technology and coding
- Helped manage other instructors in the classroom

07/2018-01-2019

Dishwasher and Prep Cook

Bonefish Grill, Southlake, TX

- Received promotion from dishwasher to food prep
- Expedited food process by portioning raw ingredients in preparation for cooking

10/2015-08/2017

Setup Crew

Whites Chapel UMC, Southlake, TX

- Lead a work group of underclassmen and formalized the event planning process
- Organized weekly events hosted by the church for members of the community

Education

08/2022present

University of North Texas

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

01/2019-05/2022

Tarrant County Community College

Associates of Science in Computer Technology

Personal Info

Address

165 Forestbrook Dr Apt 936

Lewisville, TX 75067

Phone

817-307-5529

E-mail

jbrekken6@gmail.com

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/jacobbrekken

Skills

Coding in C++



Coding in Java



Sys Admin



Certificates

- OSHA 2017
- Autodesk 2017

Activities

- Vex Robotics Team Captain and Software Lead
- National Technical Honor Society

Awards

• 1st place in the Vex Robotics Texas State Championship in 2017